

OLEKSANDR SUPRUN

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

+380936398187

suprun.energoatom@gmail.com

<u>github</u>

<u>linkedin</u>

Odesa, Ukraine

TECH SKILS

- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- REST API
- Node.js
- Express
- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GIT
- Webpack/Parcel

SOFT SKILS

- Strong analytical thinking
- Teamwork
- Comunication
- Determined
- Honest

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian — native Russian — native English — intermediate

SUMMARY

Highly motivated junior front - end developer. Looking for a full-time or part-time job as a software developer in an IT company. Have 11 years practice in studying and learning new techniques. Have a PhD degree in chemistry. I also had experience in designing, planning, managing and carrying out small scientific research. Participated in and organized international scientific conferences. For now I am passionately interested in further personal development in IT.

PROJECTS

Filmoteka

Educational project about searching movies, and adding favorite movies to a client personal library. Using pure JS, npm-packages and SCSS. Role - developer. Code link.

IceCream

Educational project Ice Cream company site. Neat and tasty design, responsible layout. Using Parcel, SCSS, JS. Role - team leader.

Code link.

Phonebook

Educational project. Using React, JS, Redux. Role - developer. Code link.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Engineer in research chemical laboratory (2016 - Present)

National Nuclear Energy Generating Company «Energoatom»

- designing, planning, managing, carring out small scientific research;
- technical documentation development;
- performing chemical analyzes and writing reports.

Lecturer at the university (2015 - 2016)

Lviv Polytechnic National University

- lecturing;
- carrying out laboratory works;
- · development of working plans and programs.

EDUCATION

IT School GolT (Kyiv) (2021-2022)

Full Stack Developer

Odessa Polytechnic National University (2015 - 2018)

Nuclear Energy. Master's degree in Nuclear Energy.

Lviv Polytechnic National University (2011 - 2015)

Technology of organic synthesis products. **PhD** degree.

Lviv Polytechnic National University (2006 - 2011)

Food chemistry. Master's degree in Fermentation Technologies.